this story is hilarious because i'm over here i'm sitting here right now
looking at my signed copy of uncle luke's album that's what i'm looking at
to amanda the diva i love you uncle luke is he's deciding that he want to drop it somewhere else
he want to drop it on the politics he want to drop it on the politics so i don't know how to
say this because i find it bonkers but i'm also all here for it so we'll just let him say it if
i do this you know uh what are the needs you know and if i do this you know are you guys in support
of it or do you like your current congress uh woman all i was thinking about the whole time he was
talking was here's the thing mccormick is a is a representative down there she's haitian
she has had a situation with investigations around her campaign her campaign finance
violations but i'm more just annoyed that she is really just one of these people that got in a
seat and ain't doing nothing one thing about uncle luke he's not here for that i really do believe
that that's somebody who would get an office and can't be bought and you know that means like
everybody's birthday they got somebody that's gonna perform for their birthday go fifth ward it's your
birthday birthday i'm all for it i would love for him to come on the show and talk about it
we are we are we are